flutetunes.com 2016-11-27

# Website Privacy Policy | flutetunes.com

Revised: February 12, 2011

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you fill out a form on our site. When using the “Contact Us” form, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third-party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative [website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

#### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To answer your questions;
  * To improve our website.

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enable the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or other's rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for advertising, or other uses.

#### Third-Party Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

#### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.flutetunes.com/terms.php) page establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy. 

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and update the Privacy Policy modification date on this page.
